securiteam.com 2019-10-10

# Beyond Security | Privacy Policies of Beyond Security

## ****

## Privacy Policy

Updated August 2018

Beyond Security, Inc (“ **Beyond**   **Security** “, “ **We** ” or “ **Us** “) is committed to protecting the privacy of you, the visitors of securiteam.com and beyondsecurity.com which is operated or owned by Beyond Security (“ **User** ” or “ **You** ” and “ **Websites** ” respectively).

This Privacy Policy (together with the Terms and any other documents referred to on it, hereinafter the “ **Policy** “), which was recently updated to align and comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“ **GDPR** “), sets out the basis on which any personal information is collected from you by us or that you provide to us, in connection with certain services provided to you through the Websites (“ **Services** “), and which will be processed by Beyond Security. By using the Services, you agree to the collection and use of your Personal Information as outlined in this Policy, if you don’t agree with this Policy, please do not use the Services.

We may amend the Policy from time to time and We will notify You of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new policy on the Websites. We encourage you to consult the Policy regularly for changes. All Capitalized terms used but not defined herein shall have the meanings given to such terms in the Terms.

### Personal Information

Our primary objective in collecting your Personal Information (as defined below) is to provide and enhance the Services and to enable you to use and enjoy the Services. We do not rent, sell, share, or trade your Personal Information with third parties other than as disclosed within this Policy.

All information provided by you or collected by us is stored on our cloud CRM of our trusted services providers as described below. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will take reasonable commercial effort to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the complete security of your data transmitted to the Websites and therefore any transmission is at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

“ **Personal Information** ” means information about you that can be used to contact or identify you. The Personal Information types collected in accordance with the Services may vary depending on the activity of each of the Websites and may include, without limitation, Information that you provides us or that is available to us through your use of the Websites or when you call us, such as your name, address, phone number, email address, country, company’s name (your employer), financial information and any other information you may decide to share with us.

Furthermore, we may also collect information about you which may include Personal Information from other sources, such as social media sites (for example – LinkedIn). Please note that such sites have their own privacy policy and you advised to carefully review those privacy policies.

In addition, we may also automatically collect information that may be produced during your use of the Websites. This information may include, your IP address, time and date of accessing the Websites.

For this purpose, we also use cookies. Cookies are small text files that you load onto your device when you visit our Websites and store the above information about yourself. We use our own cookies, but we may also use cookies and tracking tools from third parties such as Google. If you would like to know more about how cookies work, which cookies process which data on our Websites for which purposes and how you can deactivate them, please refer to the “Cookies” section below for an overview of all cookies and third-party tools embedded into our Websites.

We also utilize a variety of tools which record activities on this Website. This information is used to improve your experience and includes no personal identifying information.

### How we use your information

We may use your Personal Information in several manners: (i) to deliver or introduce you with our products and Services; (ii) to be able to contact you regarding our potential mutual engagement or order; and (iii) to fulfill your specific requests or payment for any order.

By agreeing to the use of the Services, you also agree to receive from us periodically emails regarding, among other things, special offers and other interesting information related to our Websites and Services. You may at any time opt-out of any of these communications by e-mailing us at [info@beyondsecurity.com](mailto:info@beyondsecurity.com).

We may also use Personal and non-personal information, both individually and combined together, to better understand the behavior of our Website, to troubleshoot technical problems, to monitor the use of the Websites and of the Services, to ensure proper functioning of our Services as well as to help improve the Services and their content and to analyze the performance of the website. However, we also process usage data in order to guarantee IT security and the operation of our systems and to prevent or detect misuse, in particular fraud. These purposes represent our legitimate interests and, if you are a user located in the European Economic Area (“EEA”), our legal basis for the processing of this Personal Information is Art. 6 (1) lit. (f) of the GDPR.

### Storing Personal Information

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed outside your country on servers which are located in the United States (certified under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield), European Union, or any other country subject to applicable law, including GDPR. We may process data both inside and outside of Europe and rely on legally-provided mechanisms to lawfully transfer data across borders. 

By approving our Terms and this Policy, you provide us with your consent to such transfer. We may also rely on an adequacy decision by the EU Commission or on data processing agreements incorporating the EU Commission Standard Contractual Clauses or, in the case of US providers, a certification under the Privacy Shield framework. If you would like to request a copy of these suitable safeguards to ensure an adequate level of protection for your Personal Information even in cases of transfers to countries outside the EU, please do so using the contact details provided in this Policy.

Your Personal Information may be retained for so long as necessary or useful to pursue any of the purposes stated herein, including for our legitimate interests, such as the duration of our business or contractual relationship; archiving of historical information; and legal requirements, including limitations periods during which a legal claim might be brought.

### Disclosure of Information

You understand and agree that we may disclose the Personal Information to third parties or governmental authorities, with or without your consent and with or without notice, under the following obligations:

  1. We are engaged with certain third parties which provide us services, including, hosting and maintenance, billing and other financial transaction processors (such as Stripe – which we use for credit card data storage and transaction), database storage (such as HubSpot, SalesForce and Google Drive) and process services (such as LinkedIn and Google Analytics). We may share your information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary for the purposes stated in this Policy unless otherwise permitted by law, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your Personal Information. Financial information will not be transmitted to unrelated third parties and will be encrypted as applicable.
  2. In case that we will be under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Information with or without your consent, and with or without notice in order to comply with any legal obligation including without limitation a subpoena, court order, or search warrant.
  3. We may disclose the Personal Information where you are performing any act in the Websites which constitutes a violation of any law or a breach of the Terms.
  4. We may also share the Personal Information in the event of a merger or asset sale/purchase transaction, and in the framework of negotiation of such transaction.

### Information in the Websites’ Blog

If you voluntarily disclose personal information in a blog on our Websites that information will be available to anyone who can access that area. We cannot control what others may do with this information. You should refrain from disclosing anything you do not want publicly known in such areas. If you wish us to remove any information you may have posted on a blog here, please contact [info@beyondsecurity.com](mailto:info@beyondsecurity.com)

### Links

This site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites. If you find an invalid or inappropriate link on our web site please report it to [info@beyondsecurity.com](mailto:info@beyondsecurity.com)

### Rights to Access and Control your Personal Information; Contact Us details

We provide many choices about the collection, use and sharing of the Personal Information, such as deleting or correcting the Personal Information. We offer you the option to control and manage the Personal Information we have about you. You are entitled to ask us to:

  1. Withdraw the consent – You may, at any time, withdraw your consent and no longer permit us to use and keep your Personal Information.
  2. Delete Data – You can ask us to erase or delete all or some of the Personal Information (e.g., if it is no longer necessary to provide Services to Personal Information).
  3. Change or Correct Personal Information – You can ask us to change, update or fix its Personal Information in certain cases, particularly if it’s inaccurate.
  4. Right to Access and/or Take your Personal Information – You can ask us for a copy of Personal Information you provided in machine readable form.
  5. Object to, Limit or Restrict the use of Personal Information – You can ask us to stop using all or some of the Personal Information (e.g., if We have no legal right to keep using it) or to limit our use of it (e.g., if the Personal Information is inaccurate or unlawfully held).

**Further, you have the right, for reasons arising from your particular situation, to object at any time to the processing of your personal data, which is processed on the basis our legitimate interests. If you object, we will no longer process your Personal Information in the future unless we can prove compelling grounds for the processing that outweigh your interests, rights and freedoms or the processing serves to assert, exercise, or defend legal claims.**

**You also have the right to object at any point in time to the processing of your data for direct marketing purposes (i.e. receiving newsletters or other direct marketing communications). If you exercise your right to objection, we will no longer use your Personal Information for sending you any marketing communications.**

Please let us know if you wish to exercise one or more of the foregoing rights. For any request please contact us by:

  1. Email to: info@beyondsecurity.com
  2. Call: +1 (800) 801-2821
  3. Postal mail to: Beyond Security, Inc.  
19925 Stevens Creek Blvd. Suite 100  
Cupertino, CA 95014

You acknowledge that by asking us to not store or process the Personal Information or by performing any of the foregoing actions, you may be prevented from using all or part of the Websites or the Services and you hereby waive any claim or demand you might have against Beyond Security in this matter.

If you believe that the process of the Personal Information is not complying with the law applicable to you or that our response has not satisfied you, you may lodge a complaint to the relevant Supervisory Authority (as defined in the GDPR).

### Lawful Bases for the Processing

If you are an EEA user, we only collect and process your Personal Information where we have lawful bases. Lawful bases include consent (where you have given consent), contract (where processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you (e.g. to deliver the Services that you have requested)) and “legitimate interests”.

Where we rely on your consent to process certain Personal Information, at any time you can withdraw the consent you have provided us by contacting us using the contact information detailed above, and where We rely on legitimate interests, we have the right to object.

### Safeguards and Security

We have put in place reasonable technical, physical, organizational, and administrative safeguards to protect personal data we may collect from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure therefore, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your Personal Information for improper purposes.

### Children

By using the Websites and approving the Terms and this Policy, you also approve that you understand that the Services provided through the Websites are not intended for children under the age of 18 and addressed solely to a natural person who is at least 18 years old. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information online or solicit data from or market to children under the age of 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at the Contact Info provided above. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

### Questions

If you have any questions about this, our practices or your dealings with us, you can contact us as detailed above (in the Contact Us section).

### Cookies

Our Website uses “cookies” to provide various functionalities. You may use them or block them as you wish through your browser preferences. This will not impact your ability to use any function on our Websites.

Below is a list of all cookies and other web tracking tools on our Websites that are either provided by us or by third parties:

  1. Our Own Cookies (so-called “ **Our Cookies** “)

We use these cookies to analyze web traffic, customize services and promote confidence in and security of the Websites. In addition, we use Our Cookies to distinguish one user from another and to determine the total number of visitors to the Websites in connection with the log files of our web server. The web usage data collected in this way helps us to receive the necessary feedback to constantly improve the Websites and to better serve users.

  1. Cookies and plugins on our Websites that transfer data to third parties (so-called “ **Third-Party Cookies** “)

In addition to Our Cookies, we also use the following Third-Party Cookies and plugins provided to us by the following parties and for the following purposes:

_Use of Google services on our Website_ _:_

The Websites use Google Analytics provided by Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 (“Google”). Google Analytics use cookies.

The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (identifier, browser Type/-version, operating system used, referral URL, shortened IP-Address, time of the server request) is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, within the member states of the European Union or in other signatory states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area, your IP address will first be shortened by Google on our Websites. For this purpose we have implemented the code “gat._anonymizeIp() ;” to ensure anonymous collection of IP addresses (so-called IP masking).

Only in exceptional cases is the complete IP address transmitted to a Google server in the USA and abbreviated there. If personal data is exceptionally transferred to the USA, a data protection level appropriate to the data protection level in the EU is ensured there by Google’s certification according to the so-called “Privacy Shield Agreement” between the EU and the USA ([https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)).

Google will use the information about your use of the Websites on our behalf within the framework of Google Analytics in order to evaluate your use of the Website, to compile reports on the Websites activities and to provide other services connected with the use of the websites and the Internet. The IP address transmitted by your browser as part of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data.

You can prevent the collection of data generated by the cookie about your use of the Websites (including IP address) by Google and its processing by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in under the following link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

Further information on the terms of use and data protection can be found at[ http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html) and <https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/>.

You can also prevent data processing here by clicking on the link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>
